{
    "id": "d3a95094fac44a24950e8b94bf7a0c4c",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am not the …………………….. bit afraid of dogs.",
            "description": "Not the least can mean ‘not at all’.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "least",
                "fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The essay with the ……………………… mistakes isn’t always the best.",
            "description": "We use fewest before plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "least",
                "fewest",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Last year I ……………………….. to water-ski.",
            "description": "Learn can be followed by an infinitive or how + infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "learnt",
                "learnt how",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to ………………………. down for a few minutes.",
            "description": "To lie down is to become horizontal.",
            "answers": [
                "lie",
                "lay",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………. days have been quite hectic.",
            "description": "We say the last few days, not the last days.",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "last few",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ………………………….. to ride a bicycle?",
            "description": "We cannot put a that-clause immediately after know. Instead we write ‘know how to’.",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "know how",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog wagged ……………………… tail.",
            "description": "Its is a possessive word like his or her.",
            "answers": [
                "its",
                "it's",
                "its'"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. out angry words at his tormenters.",
            "description": "In American English both spit and spat can be used as past tense and past participle of spit.",
            "answers": [
                "spit",
                "spat",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I understood her ………………………….. her strange accent.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. We use it before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "however",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have bought some eggs in case she ……………………. to dinner.",
            "description": "We normally use a present tense after in case to refer to the future.",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "stays",
                "will stay"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………….. Mumbai at 4 am.",
            "description": "Arrive can be followed by in or at.",
            "answers": [
                "arrive at",
                "arrive to",
                "arrive in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We landed ………………………… Mumbai in the morning.",
            "description": "Land can be followed by at or in.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}